export default
[{
  "id": "1",
  "question": "ALU stands for?",
  "a": "Arithmetic Logic Unit",
  "b": "Application Logic Unit",
  "c": "Array Logic Unit",
  "d": "None of These",
  "answer": "a"
}, {
  "id": "2",
  "question": "The Brain of Computer System is",
  "a": "ALU",
  "b": "CPU",
  "c": "Memory",
  "d": "None of These",
  "answer": "b"
}, {
  "id": "3",
  "question": "What difference does the 5th generation computer have from other generation computers?",
  "a": "Technological Advancement",
  "b": "Object Oriented Programming",
  "c": "Scientific Code",
  "d": "All of the above",
  "answer": "d"
}, {
  "id": "4",
  "question": "Which of the following computer generation uses concept of artificial intelligence?",
  "a": "First Generation",
  "b": "Second Generation",
  "c": "Third Generation",
  "d": "Fourth Generation",
  "answer": "d"
}, {
  "id": "5",
  "question": "When a key is pressed on keyboard, which standard is used for converting the keystroke into the corresponding bits?",
  "a": "ANSI",
  "b": "ASCII",
  "c": "EBCDIC",
  "d": "ISO",
  "answer": "b"
}, {
  "id": "6",
  "question": "Which device is used as the standard pointing device in a Graphical User Environment?",
  "a": "Keyboard",
  "b": "Mouse",
  "c": "Joystick",
  "d": "Trackball",
  "answer": "b"
}, {
  "id": "7",
  "question": "Which of the following is a valid storage type?",
  "a": "CPU",
  "b": "Keyboard",
  "c": "Pen Drive",
  "d": "Track Ball",
  "answer": "c"
}, {
  "id": "8",
  "question": "The section of the CPU that is responsible for performing mathematical operations",
  "a": "Memory",
  "b": "Register Unit",
  "c": "Control Unit",
  "d": "ALU",
  "answer": "d"
}, {
  "id": "9",
  "question": "Any storage device added to computer beyond the immediately usable main storage is known as:",
  "a": "Floppy Disk",
  "b": "Hard Disk",
  "c": "Backing store",
  "d": "Punched Card",
  "answer": "a"
}, {
  "id": "10",
  "question": "The list of coded instuctions is called",
  "a": "Computer Program",
  "b": "Algorithm",
  "c": "Flowchart",
  "d": "Utility Program",
  "answer": "a"
}]